livesportsreviews.com 2016-06-17

# Privacy Policy | Live Sports Reviews

Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and share data and information collected when you visit LiveSportsReviews.com. By visiting the site and using the services, you agree to terms of this privacy policy. We can be reached via [Contact Us](http://www.livesportsreviews.com/contact-us/) in case you have any questions regarding the privacy policy, terms and conditions.

 **COOKIES**

We might set access cookies which might be stored on your computer upon your first visit to LiveSportsReviews.com. “Cookie” is a small file which contains small text, used by the majority of the websites, sent and store on your computer’ hard driver in order to uniquely identify the browser you are using, whereas most of the current generation browsers are usually set up to accept cookies by default. You can change the cookies preferences through your browser settings.

 **THIRD PART COOKIES**

At LiveSportsReviews.com, we use third party vendors, for example, google, which use cookies to serve advertisement which might be based on your previous visit to the site.

You can read more about how google uses cookies and how you can opt-out by visiting [google advertising terms](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

 **ANALYTICS TOOLS**

At LiveSportsReviews.com we use google analytics to collect data and information of how visitors use LiveSportsReviews.com by collecting only non-personal information which include information like what url you came to LiveSportsReviews, IP Address, type of computer and browser, time spent on the site, number of pages accessed at LiveSportsReviews and what URL you exited from etc.

You can use Google Analytics Opt-out [Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) to prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics. You can read more about this on google analytic opt-out page.

 **EXTERNAL LINKS:**

[LiveSportsReviews.com](http://www.livesportsreviews.com/) might contain links to external sites. We are not in any way responsible for privacy and terms of such websites. So you have to review their privacy terms and conditions yourself.

You can always reach out to us if you have any questions about how the data collected through the use of cookies is used and stored at LiveSportsReviews.com or if you want to know more about our privacy policies. Use the [Contact Us](http://www.livesportsreviews.com/contact-us/) page for any questions.
